libgig.com 2017-05-15

# Privacy Policy - LIBGIG

At LibGig, the privacy and confidentiality of user information is important. We are committed to maintaining the privacy and security of your user information. We may update this policy from time to time, so please check here frequently. LibGig will not disclose identifiable user information to any third party without consent.

LibGig is committed to safeguarding your privacy while visiting the LibGig website, namely, [www.libgig.com](https://www.libgig.com/) (hereinafter all identified URLs are collectively referred to as the “site”). Our goal is to provide you with an Internet experience that delivers the information, resources and services that are most relevant to you. To achieve this goal, part of the operation of the site includes the gathering of certain types of information about site users. Because we understand that your privacy is important, we wish to explain the types of information we gather and the way in which we use it. This Privacy Policy applies to the site.

This Privacy Policy covers two types of information gathered at the site, personal and aggregated. The term “personal information” refers to data you voluntarily provide in connection with use of the site that identifies you and/or the company on whose behalf you are accessing and using the site. Personal information includes, e.g., data submitted in connection with our services, such as your name, e-mail address, phone number, company affiliation, physical address and/or certain other personal information.

The term “aggregated data” refers to general information regarding visitors and users of the site that relates to use of the site, e.g., traffic patterns, number of visits to certain pages, visits from other web sites or to third-party web sites linked to the site, use of particular services and interest in services, information or features of the site or other parties made available through or found at the site.

## **What information is collected about you? When do we collect it and how do we use it?**

We take the utmost care to ensure that the personal information we obtain from you is not used in a way that you may be unaware of or not agreeable to. We collect information when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter or email list, respond to a survey, or fill out a form on our site. In response, we may ask for information such as your name, email, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your LibGig experience.  In the event you opt to provide us with this information, we will only use it for the purpose specified by you at the bottom of the information gathering form. Information collected on the site may be used to:

  * Register you as a job applicant
  * Process your transactions
  * Enter your email in our promotions or sweepstakes
  * Send marketing communications or surveys to you
  * Respond to your questions or suggestions
  * Improve the quality of your visit to the site

All forms will provide an opt-out button to allow you to choose not to participate in LibGig lists and future online marketing. In deciding whether or not to join such lists, please note that they are only used for LibGig purposes or in joint promotions with a LibGig partner. We do not sell, rent or share any of your personal information with any other party including any third-party joint promoters, nor use it for unapproved commercial purposes. You may request to be removed from our lists at any time. All emails distributed to our lists will contain easy, online access to unsubscribe.

## **Permission for Use**

LibGig may collect and use personal information that you submit at the site in any manner that is consistent with uses stated in this Privacy Policy or disclosed elsewhere at the site at the point you submit such personal information. At the time you submit personal information or make a request, the intended use of the information you submit will be apparent in the context in which you submit it and/or because the site states the intended purpose. By submitting personal information at the site, you are giving your consent and permission for any use that is consistent with uses stated in this Privacy Policy or disclosed elsewhere at the site at the point you submit such personal information, and such consent will be presumed by LibGig, unless you state otherwise at the time you submit the personal information. Please do not request any such communications on behalf of an individual or company if you are not authorized to make the request.

## **Secure Registrations**

If you decide to submit an application or register at the site, you will be linked to a registration interface and our resume software. This site has measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

## **Protecting Your Information**

LibGig would like site visitors to feel confident about using the site to search for positions, comment on stories, post to the forum, craft original blogs and register/submit resumes, so LibGig is committed to protecting the information we collect. LibGig has implemented a security program to keep information that is stored in our systems protected from unauthorized access.

We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

## **Withdrawing Consent to Use**

If, after permitting use of your personal information, you later decide that you no longer want LibGig to include you on its mailing list or otherwise contact you or use your personal information in the manner disclosed in this Privacy Policy or at the site, simply tell us by sending an e-mail, or by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” button at the bottom of our email communication to you.

## **Use of Aggregated Data**

LibGig is interested in improving the site and may develop and offer new features and services. We monitor aggregated data regarding use of the site for marketing purposes and to study, improve and promote use of the site. In connection with such purposes, LibGig may share aggregated data with third parties collectively and in an anonymous way. Disclosure of aggregated data does not reveal personal information about individual site users in any way that identifies who they are or how to contact them.

## **Exceptions to the Privacy Policy**

LibGig has two exceptions to these limits on use of personal information:

  1. LibGig may monitor and, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is required, disclose information to protect the security, property, assets and/or rights of LibGig from unauthorized use, or misuse, of the site or anything found at the site.
  2. LibGig may disclose information when required by law; however, only to the extent necessary and in a manner that seeks to maintain the privacy of the individual.

## **Use of Cookies**

To enable features at the site, LibGig may assign one or more “cookies” to your Internet browser. Cookies, among other things, speed navigation through our site, keep track of information so that you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and may provide you with customized content. A cookie is an Internet mechanism composed of a small text file containing a unique identification number that permits a web server to send small pieces of information or text by means of your browser and place them on your computer’s hard drive for storage. This text lets the web server know if you have previously visited the web page. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to find out the identity of any user.

We use cookies to:

  * Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
  * Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.
  * Keep track of advertisements.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

While in the process of browsing our site, you also provide us with information that doesn’t reveal your personal identity — what type of destination you’re exploring, for example. We use this aggregated data only as explained in this Privacy Policy. We do not connect aggregated data to any name, address, or other identifying information.

You may occasionally receive cookies from unaffiliated companies or organizations, to the extent they place advertising on our site or are linked to the site. These third-party cookies may collect information about you when you “click” on their advertising or content or link. This practice is standard in the Internet industry. Because of the way in which the Internet operates, we cannot control collection of this information by these third parties, and these cookies are not subject to this Privacy Policy.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

## **Links Provided To Other Sites**

LibGig may provide links to a number of other web sites that we believe might offer you useful information and services. However, those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as LibGig. Therefore, we are not responsible for the privacy policies or the actions of any third parties, including without limitation, any web site owners whose sites may be reached through this site, nor can we control the activities of those web sites. We urge you to contact the relevant parties controlling these sites or accessing their on-line policies for the relevant information about their data collection practices before submitting any personal information or other sensitive data.

## **Google**

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

We have implemented the following:

  * Remarketing with Google AdSense
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * Demographics and Interests Reporting
  * DoubleClick Platform Integration

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

Opting out:

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

## **California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy.

– See more at: <http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf>

## **According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:**

Users can visit our site anonymously.

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:

  * On our Privacy Policy Page

Users are able to change their personal information:

  * By emailing us
  * By calling us
  * By logging in to their account

## **How does our site handle do not track signals?**

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

## **Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**

It’s also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking

## **COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

## **Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

We will notify the users via email

  * Within 7 business days

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

## **CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to:

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
  * Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
  * We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:

  * NOT use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  * Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at: [contact@libgig.com](mailto:contact@libgig.com).

  * Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

## **Your Consent To This Privacy Policy**

Use of the site signifies your consent, as well as the consent of the company for whom you use the site and whose information you submit (if any), to this on-line Privacy Policy, including the collection and use of information by LibGig, as described in this statement, and also signifies agreement to the terms of use for the site. Continued access and use of the site without acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy relieves LibGig from responsibility to the user.

## **Policy Modifications & Contacting LibGig**

LibGig reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time; notice of changes will be published on this page. Changes will always be prospective, not retroactive. If you have questions about our policies, please contact us at [contact@libgig.com](mailto:contact@libgig.com), with the words “Privacy Policy” in the subject line.
